Guide to the Michael Ellis Papers, 1937-1985 CTC.1977.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Michael Ellis Papers
1937-1985
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Ellis, Michael
CTC.1977.02
18 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
Michael Ellis was the owner-director of the Bucks County Playhouse in Pennsylvania for 11 years, and also produced 16 Broadway plays, most notably the hit Come Blow Your Horn and Two's Company starring Bette Davis. This collection includes his business records, programs, scripts, photos, scrapbooks, and correspondence.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Michael Ellis, 1977-1985. In 1981, Mr. Ellis sent Dorothy P. White's (his mother-in-law) investment records to the Curtis Collection. The materials in the Addition series were presented by Aaron Kozak Schwartz and Company, at the request of Michael Ellis, in 1983.
Related Material
For Bucks County programs, see Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pennsylvania Theatre Programs, 1870-present, CTC.1966.04, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Scope and Content Notes
The Michael Ellis Papers include correspondence, program, clippings, photographs, miscellaneous production records, miscellaneous financial records, playscripts, scrapbooks, etc., all pertaining to his long career in the theatre, as performer, stage manager, director, and particularly as producer. Comprising the core of the collection are the files on sixteen plays Mr. Ellis produced on Broadway and Off-Broadway, from 1948 to 1969. Also included are files on five additional plays which he considered seriously but from which he later withdrew, 1965-67, miscellaneous files pertaining to his company, Michael Ellis Productions, 1964-67, those covering the preceding period as owner-director of Bucks County Playhouse, 1954-64, and his early career, with early plays well documented in the scrapbooks. The papers, while not complete, do provide and extensive record of a lifetime devoted to the theatre.
After her death in 1981, Mr. Ellis sent Dorothy P. White's (his mother-in-law) investment records to the Curtis Collection. These have been filed with the appropriate plays in Series VIII, the folders labeled Dorothy P. White file; for some plays, Mrs. White's files provide the only financial record we have. The Kozak Schwart records were also added to the collection in 1983. They detail the financial records of two investment companies.
Previous Citation
Michael Ellis Papers, 1937-1985, CTC.1977.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Michael Ellis Papers, 1937-1985, CTC.15, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 14 series:
Series I. Personal File
Series II. Early Stage Career
Series III. Broadway Stage Manager
Series IV. Bucks County Playhouse
Series V. Michael Ellis Productions
Series VI. Parker Playhouse
Series VII. Magician
Series VIII. Broadway and Off-Broadway Productions
Series IX. Plays Considered for Production
Series X. Scripts
Series XI. Sheet Music
Series XII. Scrapbooks
Series XIII. Oversized Miscellany
Series XIV. Addition
Biography
Michael Ellis was born Mayer Ellis Abrahamson, on October 25, 1917, in Philadelphia, to Alexander and Mollie (Fein) Abrahamson. He attended the Wyoming Seminary in Kingston, Pennsylvania between the years 1930-1935. Later he attended the University of Grenoble, the Sorbonne, Dartmouth College, and Drew University.
Mr. Ellis first appeared on a professional stage in September 1941 for a stock production of Flight to the West in Yardley, Pennsylvania. Subsequently, he performed in several other productions most notably on Broadway in Finian's Rainbow. He was also a stage manager on that production, which opened at the 46 Street Theatre on January 10, 1947.
He began producing Broadway productions in the late 1940s. Along with James Russo, he produced The Last Dance. That show opened at the Belasco Theatre on January 10, 1948. Ellis was a stage manager for Magnolia Alley (Mansfield Theatre, April 18, 1949), Alive and Kicking (Winter Garden, January 17, 1950), and the 1951 revival of Diamond Lil starring Mae West. One of his most notable productions was Two's Company (Alvin Theatre, December 15, 1952) with Bette Davis. That production was Bette Davis' return to Broadway after an absence of 12 years. James Russo was also a co-producer for that show.
Michael Ellis held the position of managing director of Bucks County Playhousein New Hope, Pennsylvania from 1954 through 1964. There, he produced approximately five new productions each season. Among the approximately forty-five new plays he produced, several later opened in New York City: The Champagne Complex, Mask and Gown, Never too Late, The Beauty Part, The Advocate, Barefoot in the Park, and Absence of a Cello. Ellis' production of Come Blow Your Horn was Neil Simon's first play to be performed on Broadway. Mr.Ellis received the Margo Jones Award in 1963 for his contribution in presenting new dramatic works.
Ellis also was managing director of the Parker Playhouse in Fort Lauderdale, Florida from 1973-1976. After 1971, Mr. Ellis resided in Florida and North Carolina. He developed an new interest in magic, and he became an accomplished performer. He was elected to the Board of the International Brotherhood of Magicians in 1985 and was the group's president from 1990-1991. Mr. Ellis passed away on October 2, 2008.
Clippings (Information artifacts); Theatrical producers and directors -- United States; Theater -- United States; Performing arts -- United States; Directors (Performing arts); Performing artists; Playwrights; Theater programs; Correspondence; Photographs; Scripts (Documents); Financial records; Sheet music; Scrapbooks; Theater; Bucks County Playhouse (New Hope, Pa.); Russo, James -- Correspondence; Parker Playhouse (Fort Lauderdale, Fla.); Ellis, Michael; Davis, Bette -- Correspondence; Slezak, Walter -- Correspondence; Godfrey, Arthur -- Correspondence; Berman, Shelley -- Correspondence; Heflin, Van -- Correspondence; Malden, Karl -- Correspondence; Horovitz, Israel -- Correspondence; Baxter, Anne -- Correspondence; Dennis, Sandy -- Correspondence; Page, Geraldine -- Correspondence; Williams, Billy Dee -- Correspondence
- Personal File, 1953-1969; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  The first series of this collection includes correspondence, 1953-69, clippings, photographs, and miscellaneous memorabilia. Correspondence is chiefly personal, but includes items pertinent to Bucks County Playhouse and/or Michael Ellis Productions. Also includes one folder of Dorothy P. White's miscellaneous memorabilia relating to Michael Ellis.
  - Short biographies, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1953, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
  - Correspondence - No dates (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Kozak, Schwartz Co. regarding personal accounts, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Settlement of mother's estate, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings - Chiefly during residence in Bucks County (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ellis' article on summer theatre (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miss Bucks County Pageant books, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilia (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dorothy P. White papers - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Michael Ellis (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Early Stage Career, 1937-1946; II.
  Michael Ellis as performer, apprentice, director. Materials include programs, newspaper clippings, etc. beginning with the Atelier Players, program, Paris, 1938, "presented by Mayer Abrahamson." Includes summer theatres in the U.S., 1939-40; My Sister Eileen tour, 1942; U.S. Army, 1943; and his first Broadway appearance, in The Duchess of Malfi in 1946. See the scrapbook in the oversized materials series for Michael Ellis' first professional stage appearance, 1941, and additional material on My Sister Eileen. See scripts series for the Nothing but the Truth playscript, directed by Ellis in Paris in 1938.
  - Atelier Players - Paris program, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cohasset Summer Theatre - Programs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Wilkes Barre - Summer Programs, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - My Sister Eileen - Sob Sister Sentinel and publication of the Eastern Company…on Tour, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Army miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Duchess of Malfi Ellis as Silvio on Broadway, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Soldier Show, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Players programs (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Broadway Stage Manager, 1946-1958; III.
  Includes the Finian's Rainbow file (programs, reviews, correspondence, photographs, etc.) and the first night program for The Body Beautiful. Michael Ellis' stage manager's books for The Body Beautiful and Magnolia Alley are filed in the Scripts series. The papers contain no record of Alive and Kicking, 1950, or Diamond Lil, 1951, for which Ellis was also stage manager.
  - Finian's Rainbow - Programs, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Publicity reviews (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Opening night telegrams (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Performers photographs (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Show recording photographs (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Unidentified photographs (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Finian's Rainbow - Miscellaneous materials (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Body Beautiful - Broadway Theatre, Jan 23, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Bucks County Playhouse, 1954-1975; IV.
  For the most part this series' materials are chiefly from the eleven year period, 1954 through 1964, but incomplete, when Ellis was owner-director of the Playhouse. Includes correspondence, local publications, clippings, financial records, etc., 1948-75. Includes one folder of correspondence, 12 items, concerns Frances Farmer, 1956-57. Bucks County materials are also located in other series of these Papers: see Series VIII and IX for Bucks County productions later considered for, or produced in, New York; Bucks Country scripts in Series X; additional material in scrapbooks 5-6, Series XII.
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and related papers, 1948-1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Frances Farmer, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Production list, 1954-1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Crucial Year for Mike Ellis - "by Marguerite Karaczan - In Bucks County Traveler, May 1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 20th Anniversary, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Buff: The Magazine of Little Theatre, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Directors' meetings minutes and related papers, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 25th Anniversary, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bucks County Arts Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - St. John Terrell - Playhouse founder photograph (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sales agreements and lease, 1948-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Financial statements and lease, 1948-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Taxes and related correspondence (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Michael Ellis Productions, 1964-1970; V.
  This series contains a miscellaneous and incomplete record of Ellis' production company. Includes material not specific to single productions including correspondence, casting, staff applications, financial records, etc.
  - Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Correspondence and memoranda (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Nat Debin (Lenny-Debin), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Derek Glynne, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Kozak, Schwartz Co., 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Leslie Lee, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Fred O'Donovan, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Kenneth Schwartz, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - American Cancer Society, Judy Holliday Fund (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Channel 13 Fifth Birthday Celebration, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Dartmouth College, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Notre Dame 1968 Sophomore National Literary Festival, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Office supplies, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Casting - Applications and resumes (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Casting - Client lists (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Casting - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Casting - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - League of New York Theatres, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - League of New York Theatres, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Scripts - Rejections (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scripts - Traffic lists (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Staff applications - Costume designers (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Staff applications - Producers and directors (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Staff applications - Secretaries (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Staff applications - Set and lighting designers (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Staff applications - Stage managers (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Staff applications - Assistants (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Staff applications - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Labor regulations - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Theatre and stock company directories, New York Drama critics list (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Theatrical services (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bank statements, 1965-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Checkbook stubs, 1968-1978 (Box 5, Folder 6-9)
  - Bills, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Insurance - policies and correspondence (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Investors - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Investors - Lists (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Investors - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Taxes - Miscellaneous, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Parker Playhouse, 1975-1976; VI.
  Miscellany pertaining to Michael Ellis' final year (1975-1976) as manager of Parker Playhouse in Fort Lauderdale, Florida.
  - Parker Playhouse materials, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Magician, 1985; VII.
  This series contains a few programs, through 1985, that include Ellis as a performing magician.
  - Magician programs (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Broadway and Off-Broadway Productions, 1948-1969; VIII.
  The productions in this series are arranged chronologically, 1948-1969. Files range in size from Courtin' Time, a single folder of photographs of the theatre marquee, Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, 42 folders, including programs, publicity, reviews, correspondence, company bills, budget, casting, contracts, photographs, etc., and the financial records of the investment company (A.K. company) including bank statements, financial statements, insurance records, investors correspondence and records and tax returns. Organization for each play is fairly similar, depending upon contents: Production history, i.e. programs, publicity, reviews; correspondence; other production information filed in alphabetical order; and financial records of the investment company, also in alphabetical order. Following is a list of the productions, each with name of investment company (if pertinent), New York opening date, and number of performances.
  1. The Last Dance. January 27, 1948. 7 performances.
  2. The Play's the Thing. April 28, 1948. 244 performances.
  3. Jenny Kissed Me. December 23, 1948. 20 performances.
  4. Courtin' Time. June 13, 1951. 37 performances.
  5. Two's Company. December 15, 1952. 91 performances.
  6. Come Blow Your Horn. Kentwood Company. February 22, 1961. 617 performances.
  7. The Beauty Part. Beautiful Company. December 26, 1962. 85 performances.
  8. The Advocate. Advocate Company. October 14, 1963. 8 performances.
  9. Absence of Cello. Cello company. September 21, 1964. 120 performances.
  10. The Paisley Convertible. Happy Bed Company. February 11, 1967.
  11. The Girl in the Freudian Slip. Slip Company. May 18, 1967. 4 performances.
  12. Sweet Eros and Witness. B.B. Company. November 21, 1968. 78 performances.
  13. Ceremonies in Dark Old Men. A.K. Company. April 28, 1969. Pocket Theatre. 320 performances.
  14. Angela. Angela Company. October 30, 1969. 4 performances.
  15. Who's Happy Now? Precious Company, November 17, 1962. 32 performances.
  - The Last Dance, 1948; 1.
    - Photographs and newspaper clippings (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Play's the Thing, 1948; 2.
    - Programs, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and reviews - New York production (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Publicity - Central City (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - New York production (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - Central City publicity (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Original New York production, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Jenny Kissed Me, 1948; 3.
    - Programs, 1948, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Publicity and reviews, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Courtin' Time, 1952; 4.
    - Photographs - Theatre marquee (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Two's Company, 1952; 5.
    - Correspondence and contract - Bette Davis, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Sammy Cahn, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Photographs - Theatre exterior (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Come Blow Your Horn, 1961; 6.
    - Bucks County production - Publicity and reviews, August 1960 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Tryout in Philadelphia - Publicity and reviews, February 2, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 18, Folder 17)
    - New York production - Opening night program with publicity and reviews, February 1961 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - London production - Opening night program with publicity and reviews, February 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1957-1962 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Kozak, Schwartz Co., 1961-1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Productions outside New York, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Kentwood Co. - Financial statements, 1963-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Kentwood Co. - Investors correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kentwood Co. - Investors correspondence acceptances, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kentwood Co. - Investors correspondence refusals, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kentwood Co. - Investors lists (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kentwood Co. - Investors: Dorothy P. White file, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 8-10)
    - Kentwood Co. - Taxes and partnership returns, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Kentwood Co. - Taxes and N.Y. State partnership returns, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Kentwood Co. - Taxes and Federal partnership statements, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Kentwood Co. - Taxes and U.S. and N.Y. partnership returns, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Beauty Part, 1962; 7.
    - Tryouts - Bucks County Program and reviews, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tryouts - New Haven program, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Tryouts - Philadelphia program and reviews, December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - New York production - Program and reviews, December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - S.J. Perelman (incl. Bucks County contracts), 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Don Walker (composer) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Noel Willman (director) - Contract and miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Noel Willman - Outstanding bills, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Noel Willman - Foreign rights, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Noel Willman - Legal, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Noel Willman - London production, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Advertising (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Advertising promotion phone record (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Budget (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Casting - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Casting - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Casting - Photographs (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Contracts - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Contracts - Edmund Anderson (associate producer) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Contracts - Actor's Equity (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Contracts - Stagehands (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Contracts - Theatres (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Photographs (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Staff applications (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stage manager's book - Without script (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Tickets - New York preview (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Tickets - Opening night requests (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Tickets - Opening night assignments (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Tickets - Group sales (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Beautiful Company - Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Beautiful Company - Financial statements, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Beautiful Company - Prospective investors correspondence (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Beautiful Company - Investors correspondence (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Beautiful Company - Investors lists and Limited Partnership Agreement form (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Beautiful Company - Investors assignments (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Beautiful Company - Investors Dorothy P. White file (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Beautiful Company - Pennsylvania Securities Commission (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Beautiful Company - Royalties (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Beautiful Company - Taxes, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Advocate, 1963; 8.
    - Productions - Bucks County Playhouse program and reviews, June 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Productions - Meineola Playhouse program and reviews, September 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Productions - ANTA Theatre program and reviews, October 14, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Abner D. Klipstein, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Tom O'Connor, Committee for the Vindication of Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Charles G. Thompson (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Estimated operating budget (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Company Director (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Contracts - Robert Noah (director) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Playscript in Theatre Arts with photographs and various drafts of article by Ellis and William Hammerstein, November 1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - TV production - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper clippings - Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Advocate Company - Investors Dorothy P. White file, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Advocate Company - Limited Partnership Agreement with Mary Ellis (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
  - Absence of Cello, 1963; 9.
    - Production publicity and reviews (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - London and Paris productions, 1964-1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Estimated operating budget (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Film rights (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Cello Company - Financial statements and correspondence, 1964-1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Cello Company - Investors correspondence and partnership distributions (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Cello Company - Investors Dorothy P. White file (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Cello Company - Taxes, 1965-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - The Paisley Convertible, 1967; 10.
    - New York production - Henry Miller Theatre Program, February 11, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Publicity reviews (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Warren Berlinger, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Harry Cauley (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Actor's Equity (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Advertising (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Bills (Box 13, Folder 11)